<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity on Odåsnac</title>
    <link>https://www.odasnac.com/tags/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity on Odåsnac</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:08:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.odasnac.com/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One brick at a time</title>
      <link>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/one-brick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/one-brick/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Today&amp;rsquo;s musings led me down a path of unexpected tranquility, reminiscent of the age-old adage: &amp;ldquo;It is one brick at a time.&amp;rdquo; A simple yet profound lesson unfolded before me, whispering the importance of the journey over the destination. In a world obsessed with outcomes, I found solace in the idea of letting go, of surrendering to the process without the haste that often clouds our judgment.
As I reflected deeper, it dawned upon me that our penchant for speed carries with it a shadow of doubt, a silent question of our own capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Second Brain</title>
      <link>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/building-a-second-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/building-a-second-brain/</guid>
      <description>Building a second brain is about creating a system to process the vast amounts of information we consume and transform it into actionable knowledge.
Building a Second Brain: A Proven Method to Organize Your Digital Life and Unlock Your Creative Potential, by Tiago Forte is one of the books of 2022.
The underlying philosophy is very similar to that of Zettelkasten. Tiago Forte’s method is a pragmatic update to this note-taking system, which is popular in the academic world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
