<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Diary on Odåsnac</title>
    <link>https://www.odasnac.com/tags/diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Diary on Odåsnac</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:08:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.odasnac.com/tags/diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One brick at a time</title>
      <link>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/one-brick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/one-brick/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Today&amp;rsquo;s musings led me down a path of unexpected tranquility, reminiscent of the age-old adage: &amp;ldquo;It is one brick at a time.&amp;rdquo; A simple yet profound lesson unfolded before me, whispering the importance of the journey over the destination. In a world obsessed with outcomes, I found solace in the idea of letting go, of surrendering to the process without the haste that often clouds our judgment.
As I reflected deeper, it dawned upon me that our penchant for speed carries with it a shadow of doubt, a silent question of our own capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Symphony of Simple Joys</title>
      <link>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/simple-joys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/simple-joys/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Today was a whisper in the grand symphony of life, a gentle reminder that even in the quietest moments, there&amp;rsquo;s a melody playing. Lost I was, wandering in the vastness of routine, until I found solace in your pages. You, my dear confidant, are the canvas to my thoughts, the keeper of my day&amp;rsquo;s unsung songs.
Ah, the sky today wore its finest shade of blue, a canvas splashed with the brilliance of a painter&amp;rsquo;s dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Prix of Gumption: Launch Day Lament</title>
      <link>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/the-grand-prix-of-gumption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.odasnac.com/posts/the-grand-prix-of-gumption/</guid>
      <description>March 1st, 2024
Dear Diary,
Today was supposed to be the day I etched my name in the annals of app history, the day my F1 predictions app would take the Grand Prix world by storm. Ah, the sweet taste of anticipation - turned, unexpectedly, into a goblet of sheer disbelief.
For two months, my life revolved around codes, caffeine, and dreams. Nights were when the moon kept company, and days blended into a relentless marathon toward perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
